TOM : And of course I set it to Icelandic time because we share
a love of the aurora borealis , Gordy .
And you have no idea how to tell time .
- ( AUDIENCE LAUGHING ) - JUPE : Great gift , Dad .
Way to think things through .
PHYLLIS : Somehow , you 'd think that a man
who can send a rocket into space would be able
to manage a halfway decent birthday present .
- Nope . - ( AUDIENCE LAUGHING )
JUPE : You know , Gordy , all things considered ,
maybe my gift isn 't so bad after all .
AUDIENCE : Aw .
- MARY JO : Hey , Gordy . Surprise ! - ( PHYLLIS GASPS )
PHYLLIS : Wow ! Now , there 's a gift .
( AUDIENCE LAUGHING )
MARY JO : Here you go , Gordy .
- Happy birthday . - ( GRUFF PANTING , GRUNTING )
PHYLLIS : Oh , beautiful , Haley .
- TOM : Aw . - ( AUDIENCE APPLAUDING )
( SHARP POP )
( DISTORTED , INDISTINCT VOICES CRYING , SPEAKING FRANTICALLY )
- ( VOICES STOP ) - ( CHILD 'S BREATH SHUDDERING )
( SHARP POP )
♪ ♪
( SHUDDERING BREATHS CONTINUE )
( QUIET , RASPY WHIMPERING )
- ( SHARP POP , OBJECT THUMPS ) - ( WHIMPERING STOPS )
- ( OBJECTS CLATTERING ) - ( GRUFF PANTING )
( CHILD 'S SHUDDERING BREATHS CONTINUE )
( HOOTING QUIETLY )
♪ ♪
( BIRDS CHIRPING )
MAN ( ON RADIO ) : Good morning on what is
sure to be a windy one .
We have a high wind warning
for the L.A. County coast and valleys
with some clouds sure to come in around 10 : 00 a.m.
And even though the high gust warning will , um , expire
mid to late morning , you 'll still want to keep ...
WOMAN ( ON RADIO ) : The search for a group of missing hikers
is set to resume this morning just outside Agua Dulce .
The tour group went out two days ago
- and on the Pacific Crest Trail . - ( HORSES NEIGHING )
But didn 't come back as expected that night .
Crews started searching yesterday morning ...
MAN 2 ( ON RADIO ) : And traffic is already backed up
due to an accident on the southbound 101 .
It is 7 : 44 with Bo and Ives .
( HORSES GRUNTING , PANTING )
( NEIGHING )
( MACHINERY WHIRRING )
OTIS SR . : Bang .
♪ ♪
( OTIS SR . CLICKS TONGUE )
Bang .
( CLICKS TONGUE )
Whoa . Come on .
( CLICKING TONGUE )
Down , down .
Down , down , down .
Bang ! Yes , a good boy .
Up . Up , up .
Okay , up . Up , up .
Got to keep our heads up out the clouds on this one .
- I know . - ( HORSE GRUNTING )
( CLICKS TONGUE )
( GRUNTS )
Now , we land this ... ( CHUCKLES )
Yeah . Like Six Guns .
I mean , we really put on a show ,
well , you know they 're gonna bring us back for the sequel .
Mm-hmm .
Well , we sure as hell ain 't got to sell no more horses .
So just execute .
And we ain 't got no more problems . Mm .
( TAKES DEEP BREATH )
You good ?
Where your sister ?
What 's that about ?
- She 's supposed to be here . - Yeah .
( SCOFFS QUIETLY )
( BREATHES DEEPLY )
♪ ♪
( STATIC CRACKLES )
( MACHINERY POWERS DOWN )
Goddamn it .
OTIS SR . : Thought I told you to fix the damn walker .
( WOMAN SCREAMING IN DISTANCE )
( SCREAMING FADES )
You hear that ?
( OBJECT WHIZZES , THUDS )
( WHIZZING , RAPID THUDDING )
( METALLIC PINGING )
♪ ♪
( NEIGHING )
OJ : Pops .
♪ ♪
- Come on , come on . Pop . - Firefly .
- What else ? What else ? - Ghost .
Uh-huh .
Beethoven .
Uh-huh , uh-huh .
- Commodore . - Yeah .
Virgil .
You good . You good .
- You good . You good . - ( GROANING )
( CHUCKLES ) : You good , man . You good .
- Ghost . - You good . You good . You good .
- Pops ? - Lucky .
- Pops . Pops . - ( SLURRING ) : Commodore .
Pops !
♪ ♪
( DEVICE BUZZING QUIETLY )
( HORSE WHINNIES )
( WIND WHISTLING )
♪ ♪
( FRANTIC CHATTER AND SCREAMING IN DISTANCE )
( GRUFF PANTING )
( SCREAMING CONTINUES )
( SCREAMING AND CHATTER FADE )
♪ ♪
( DISTORTED SCREAMING )
( DISTORTED SCREAMING FADES )
♪ ♪
( QUIET CHATTER )
( MUSIC PLAYING FAINTLY )
BUSTER : OJ .
Oh . Hi , horsie .
OJ : Hey , hey , hey . Don 't look him in the eyes , please .
BUSTER : Okay .
You ready to do the safety meeting ?
OJ : Uh , I 'm gonna need like five ...
Um , my team 's almost here .
BUSTER : Your team 's not here .
- Okay . Hold . - ( FYNN LAUGHING )
Sorry , I got the horse guy talking to me , too .
- What 's up ? Copy . - FYNN : Safety meeting at the ...
BUSTER : Ladies and gentlemen , Ms. Bonnie Clayton on set .
- Here she is , everybody . - ( APPLAUSE )
- Take a look at all of that . - ( BONNIE WHOOPS )
( FYNN LAUGHING )
BUSTER : Fynn , this is OJ , our horse trainer .
You remember these guys from Flash Point .
Yeah . Hi .
Uh ...
Your name is OJ ?
Yeah , Otis Junior .
Oh .
Uh ...
Where 's the o .. The other guy ?
- The-the-the senior guy ? - Dude , he died .
About six months ago .
A bunch of random shit fell out of a plane .
So I guess we 're stuck with Junior over here .
- No . - Yeah .
( SIGHS ) Okay .
Fuck . Great .
Uh , Ant , how we looking ?
Yeah , good , if we 're selling a horse 's ass .
( LAUGHS ) That 's , uh ,
legendary cinematographer Antlers Holst over here ...
Let 's go ahead and spin the horse .
But you had said " hold , " so ...
- And now I 'm saying " spin . " Let 's go . - ( CLICKS TONGUE )
FYNN : Great . And while that 's spinning , can we get makeup ?
BUSTER : Get makeup for Ms. Bonnie Clayton , please .
Hold on .
Can you step away from the back , please ?
MAKEUP ARTIST : They told me to come here .
Good call , OJ . Um , tell you what ,
let 's do a quick safety meeting .
Guys , this is OJ , our horse trainer .
Take it away .
Kill the music , please .
- ( MUSIC STOPS ) - ( CHATTER QUIETS )
My name is OJ . Uh ...
I think my sister 's gonna be here in a minute .
GRIZZ : Little louder , please . We cannot hear you in the back .
( LOUDER ) : I said we are animal wranglers
with Haywood Hollywood Horses .
And , uh ... did you know the very first , uh , assem ...
EMERALD : Hey , yo !
( PANTING ) : Excuse me . Sorry .
I 'm so sorry about that . Let me do that .
Sorry , brother .
- Safety meeting . - Yeah .
- ( CLEARS THROAT ) - ( BUSTER CLEARS THROAT )
Hello ! How y 'all doing ?
Sorry for the tardiness .
My name is Emerald , that 's OJ ,
and we are your animal wranglers today
with Haywood Hollywood Horses .
Now , did you know that the very first
assembly of photographs in sequential order
to create a motion picture
was a two-second clip of a Black man on a horse ?
Yes , it was . Yes , it was . Look it up .
Now , I know you guys know Eadweard Muybridge ,
the grandfather of motion pictures
who took the pictures that created that clip ,
but does anybody know the name of the Black jockey
that rode the horse ?
No .
Nope ? I mean , the very first stuntman ,
animal wrangler and movie star all rolled into one ,
and there is literally no record of him .
That man was a Bahamian jockey
that went by the name of Alistair E. Haywood .
And he is my great-great-grandfather .
- Great . - There 's another " great " grandfather .
That 's why back at the Haywood Ranch ,
as the only Black-owned horse trainers in Hollywood ,
we like to say , " Since the moment pictures could move ,
we had skin in the game . "
( LAUGHS )
All right , let 's get into some , uh , safety precautions
while we 're on set , shall we ?
Number one , please refrain from making any loud noises ,
sudden movements , and keep your cell phones off .
We 'd really appreciate that .
Two , if you see anything that looks or feels unsafe ,
contact me , OJ or your second in chain of command .
And three , let 's have a great shoot !
- ( SCATTERED APPLAUSE ) - Uh , and I 'm Emerald Haywood .
I direct , write , produce , act .
I do a little ... ♪ Singing on the side . ♪
Uh , motorcycles , baby .
Look , I-I make a mean grilled cheese
if you 're looking for crafty .
- Just-just holler at me . - ( APPLAUSE )
FYNN : Okay , that was great .
That was ... that was a lot .
Uh , let 's do a rehearsal .
- Yeah ? Rehearsal ? - BUSTER : Rehearsing , we should .
We should do one . Rehearsing .
I think ... I think he might need a break .
BUSTER : Yeah , we 'll rehearse one first ,
and then break , yeah ?
Well , I 'm ready to do one .
FYNN : OJ , she 's ... she 's ready to do one .
Tell the horse we 're ready to do one .
VFX , can we get the ball in here while we have a sec ?
- Em . - FYNN : VFX . Uh , and , OJ ,
you can ... you can step off .
Step out . Step off .
- Yeah , yeah . - Uh , step out .
OJ : Em ?
What 's the horse 's name ?
- Uh , Lucky . - Lucky .
- Is he ? - FYNN : VFX !
Yeah . Em ?
- FYNN : Uh , OJ , let 's step off . - You calling me ?
- Hey , hey , hey , hey , hey , hey . - MAKEUP : I 'm trying to work .
OJ : What 'd I tell you about that , man ?
FYNN : Hey , man , if she can 't get near the back of the horse ,
- what are we doing here ? - Hey , hey , hey , hey ! - ( NEIGHS )
- ( SCREAMS ) Whoa ! - Whoa , whoa , whoa , whoa , whoa ,
- whoa , whoa , whoa , whoa , whoa , whoa . - Medic .
Whoa , whoa , whoa , whoa .
- Are you okay ? - Whoa , whoa .
( WATER RUNNING )
( SIGHS )
♪ ♪
GRIZZ : Look , maybe it 's just too soon , huh ?
Yeah , it 's not the gig . Not ready yet .
Right ?
- We need it , man . - No , I know .
Your dad left an enormous hole . I know that .
But don 't worry , there 'll be others .
All right ? I 'm sorry .
- And ... - Sorry .
Just , you tell her sorry .
Thank you for the opportunity .
Come on , now .
FYNN : Oh , where 's VFX ?
GRIZZ : Oh , all right . You got it .
- Sorry , that was ... - ( BUSY CHATTER )
So , where am I dropping you ?
- I 'm-a go up with you . - ( SIGHS )
I need to get some shit .
My little girl said , you know , I could crash at her place ,
so I 'll be gone in the morning .
So I 'm gonna drive you back tomorrow ?
I can find a ride .
But , I mean , like , can I get fun OJ out this bitch ?
' Cause this wack-ass OJ
is really making me feel like I 'm not loved .
Is that how you want your little sister to feel ?
♪ ♪
- ( INDISTINCT CHATTER ) - ( ORCHESTRAL MUSIC PLAYING )
EMERALD : What happened to Gold Rush ?
OJ : Gold Rush went bankrupt .
It 's been this for three years .
- EMERALD : Damn . - WOMAN : Howdy , folks .
Welcome to Jupiter 's Claim .
MAN : Step on up for the wishing well .
Get your Jupe Jangle .
Go on , take a picture at the well .
( CHUCKLES )
AMBER ( OVER SPEAKERS ) : Cowboys and cowgirls ,
just a little heads-up .
Join us Fridays at 5 : 30 p.m. for the brand-spanking-new .
Jupiter 's Claim Star Lasso Experience .
WOMAN 2 : Come on over to the Sundae Saloon .
Get your ice-cold sarsaparilla .
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
MAN : Look at this . I 've never seen anything like it .
( CLANKING )
( CLICKS , SNAPS )
- Oh , shi ... - Come on .
I 'm sorry , y 'all . I 'm sorry .
- Photo bomb . - You ruined it .
- Yeah , my bad . - Gold , I tell you .
They got gold up in here .
OJ : Lucky .
Hang tight .
I 'll be back .
MAN : Let 's go .
♪ ♪
( PLAYFUL CHATTER )
( OJ SIGHS )
How many you sold ?
How many ?
Ten .
You sold ten of Pops ' horses ?
I 'm gonna get ' em back .
- Can you stay out here ? - Why ?
I 'm developing a business relationship ,
and you 're a liability right now .
How am I a liability ?
How are you a lia ...
Don 't promote your fucking side shit on the job .
- Oh , my God . - Actor , singer , dancer ,
seamstress , motorcycles .
You want to promote something , promote this business .
No , OJ . No .
First of all , that 's not my side shit . This is .
And second of all , if anybody 's a liability ... ( CHUCKLES )
- Fuck you . - No , fuck you .
AMBER : Hi there . It 's Amber again from Jupe 's Claim .
It does look like we were able to squeeze out , uh ,
a couple of extra press passes
for the upcoming friends and family preview .
Oh . No apology necessary .
This is in reference to the biggest , bestest ,
brand-new live show we have coming up here at the park ,
- which is sneaking up on us ... - MAN : Come in .
AMBER : If you 'd like , I can go ahead and put you down ...
MAN : ( CLEARS THROAT ) OJ .
Thanks for coming up .
How you doing ? This is my sister Em .
Hi there .
So , uh ... who 'd you bring me ?
Uh , Lucky .
He 's my second-best horse , you know , uh ...
He lost focus .
So , uh ... I mean , I did , too , but I can 't fire myself .
- ( CHUCKLES ) That 's good . - EMERALD ( STAMMERING ) : Hold up .
This you ?
You literally the Asian kid from Kid Sheriff ?
- Em , Em , Em , Em ... - MAN : No , it 's okay .
Yeah , I was , uh ... I was Lil ' Jupe .
Ah , dude , you were literally my favorite .
You mind if I get a picture real quick ?
Hey , you mind if we talk ?
Yes . Of course .
Please , browse away .
Su casa es mi casa .
Thank you . I sure will .
JUPE : Um , so ...
same deal , yeah ? Eleven-five ?
- OJ : Yeah . Thank you . - EMERALD : That 's 3D . Yeah .
Whatever happened to that Black boy ? He was good .
Stop , stop .
- ( JUPE CLEARS THROAT ) - He was good .
I actually wanted to , uh , lay some groundwork ,
uh , to a pathway of-of , uh , buying some of them back .
All right ?
- Yeah . - Mm-hmm .
Yeah . Totally .
Um ...
- Yeah . - Yeah ?
JUPE : Actually , OJ ,
the offer I made your dad is still on the table .
OJ : Oh , uh ...
- JUPE : Let me ... Let ... - Yo , wait a minute .
So , that ...
OJ , have I shown you this ?
This is in reference to the Gordy 's Home incident .
( SIGHS )
Gordy 's Home . Yeah , yeah .
So , Gordy 's Home is a short-lived but fabled sitcom
I starred in in ' 96 after Kid Sheriff blew up .
Yeah , my pops told me about this show .
The-the monkey went crazy or some shit .
You know , I usually charge a fee for this .
EMERALD : Oh , damn .
JUPE : Ta-da .
EMERALD : Hmm .
( MUSIC PLAYING QUIETLY )
JUPE : That 's the first exploding fist bump .
EMERALD : What ? Really ?
Y 'all came up with that ?
So , as I was saying , uh , Gordy 's Home began airing
- in the fall of ' 96 ... - ( OJ SIGHS LOUDLY )
... and it was an immediate hit .
Uh , ratings were huge .
Pretty good reviews .
Just really took off .
Yeah .
Then , uh , one day ...
( CLEARS THROAT ) ... we were shooting an episode
in season two entitled , uh , " Gordy 's Birthday . "
And , um ... boom .
One of the chimps that plays Gordy just ...
just hit his limit .
And it was six minutes and 13 seconds of havoc .
Network tried to bury hit , but it was a spectacle .
People are just obsessed . ( CHUCKLES )
You 're kidding me .
OJ , you said you heard about that ?
Mm-hmm . That 's why they don 't let you use chimps .
That 's part of the reason .
There 's a growing Gordy 's Home fan base out there now .
This Dutch couple paid me 50K
to come in here and spend the night .
( CHUCKLES ) I didn 't ask .
That 's crazy .
( JUPE GRUNTS )
( INDISTINCT SITCOM CHATTER OVER TV )
So , what happened really , man ?
You haven 't seen the Bad Gordy sketch on SNL ?
I mean , they pretty much nailed it better than I could .
- EMERALD : Mm . - No ?
Saturday Night Live ?
Darrell Hammond as Tom .
Ana Gasteyer as Phyllis .
Cheri Oteri as Mary Jo Elliot .
Scott Wolf is the host . He 's me .
But , of course , the star of the sketch
is Chris goddamn Kattan as Gordy ,
and he is ...
undeniable , okay ?
Bit goes like this .
Everyone 's trying to celebrate Gordy 's birthday ,
but every time Gordy hears something about the jungle ,
Gordy .. Kattan .. Goes off .
( CHUCKLES ) And it 's ... it 's Kattan .
He 's just crushing it .
He is a force of nature .
He is killing on that stage .
- ( SHUDDERING BREATHS ) - ( MARY JO WHEEZING )
( SIGHS ) Yeah .
It 's legendary .
Legendary shit .
( LAUGHS ) Yeah .
Yeah , I 'm gonna have to go ahead ,
- look that one up on YouTube . - ( JUPE CHUCKLES )
Details , you know ?
JUPE : Totally .
♪ ♪
( EMERALD SIGHS )
OJ : I got some work I got to do .
So we ain 't gonna chill tonight , nothing ?
- You want to work ? - Hell no .
( EMERALD SIGHS )
So , uh , what was the offer ?
- Jupe ? - Yeah .
He offered to buy the ranch .
Oh , really ? ( CHUCKLES )
That 's interesting . How much ?
Why ?
' Cause ... I 'm trying to see how big of a dumb-ass you are .
Big dumb-ass , probably . ( CHUCKLES )
( EMERALD SIGHS )
So I guess you don 't want to see what 's good
with Dad liquor cabinet , then , huh ? !
I got that hobby weed , too , actually .
That 's all you had to say , then .
- ( CLAPS ) - The hobby weed .
That 's all you had to say , just let me know .
You should 've dropped that at the top .
" I got the hobby weed . " You know I 'm ready .
♪ If you see me walking down the street ♪
♪ And I start to cry each time we meet ... ♪
Okay , your reflexes are still quick . Like , whoa .
- I ain 't mad at it . - I 'm watching .
- ♪ Walk on by ♪ - EMERALD : To the man .
♪ Make believe ♪
Drink .
♪ That you don 't see the tears ♪
♪ Just let me grieve in private ... ♪
Oh , shit .
Remember Jean Jacket ?
- OJ : Yeah , good horse . - ( EMERALD SIGHS )
EMERALD : Supposed to be my first horse , actually .
I was just talking to my therapist about this
- not too long ago . - Therapist ?
Yes . I fuck one on occasion sometimes .
♪ Walk on by ... ♪
I was telling her that , for my ninth birthday ,
I was supposed to get to train Jean Jacket .
But then Pops got some Western , and ...
Jean Jacket wasn 't mine no more .
Classic Otis Senior .
I distinctly remember
standing right here at this window ,
watching y 'all train my horse .
My horse .
♪ ♪
Pops never looked up at me .
OTIS SR . : Whoa , now .
Whoa , now . Whoa , now .
OJ , come on .
But you did , nigga .
Remember ?
It was Scorpion King , actually .
It wasn 't a Western .
That was the first job Pops took me on .
Wasn 't much fun .
Ended up using camels anyways , so ...
The point is ...
Yeah , fuck the point .
Yo , that man was hardheaded as fuck .
And so are you .
That 's it .
( SIGHS )
( CHUCKLES )
But at the end of the day , you got to ...
you got to admit , man , Pops ...
Pops did something when he made this place .
He changed the industry .
That 's real .
I can 't just let that go .
Why is Ghost in the arena ?
( GHOST SPUTTERS SOFTLY )
( COYOTES HOWLING FAINTLY IN DISTANCE )
What 's good ?
Yeah .
( WIND GUSTING SOFTLY )
- ( GHOST SPUTTERS ) - ( DOGS BARKING IN DISTANCE )
( " THIS IS THE LOST GENERATION " BY THE LOST GENERATION PLAYING )
Hey , yo , Em . Em !
Turn it down !
All right !
♪ Your generation believed in talk ♪
♪ Scared of the very steps in which ... ♪
( GHOST NEIGHS )
( SONG CONTINUES IN DISTANCE )
EMERALD : Hey !
Where he going ?
- ( INSECTS TRILLING ) - ( FAINT , DISTANT HOWLING )
( DISTANT HOWLING CONTINUES )
JUPE ( OVER SPEAKERS , FAINTLY ) : What if I ...
( ECHOING ) : What if I told you
you 'll leave here different ?
See , every Friday for the last six months
my family and I bore witness
to an absolute
( DISTORTED ) : Spectacle .
( HOOFBEATS GALLOPING )
( WIND GUSTING )
( WILD SHRIEKING IN DISTANCE )
- ( WIND GUSTING STRONGER ) - ( SHRIEKING CONTINUES )
( MUSIC CONTINUES )
( MUSIC SLOWS AND DISTORTS )
- ( WILD SHRIEKING IN DISTANCE ) - Huh ?
( MUSIC RETURNS TO NORMAL )
( MUSIC CONTINUES IN DISTANCE )
( DISTANT SHRIEKING )
♪ ♪
( ENGINE STOPS )
EMERALD : You see it ? The power ?
Where 's Ghost ?
- I don 't know . - Hold on .
Boom . Power went out .
- See ? - Rewind .
Stop .
Ghost talking about , " I ain 't listening .
I 'm not trained . I do whatever the fuck I want . "
What ?
What 'd you see ?
OJ : What 's a bad miracle ?
Hmm ?
They got a word for that ?
Nope .
They said it was a prop plane or something that killed Pops .
That shit ain 't never made sense to me .
Then tonight , I heard Ghost make a sound
I ain 't never heard a horse make .
What did you see ? Hmm ?
It was big .
- How big ? - Big .
- What 'd it look like ? - I don 't know .
( EMERALD SIGHS )
It was fast .
Too fast .
Too quiet to be a plane .
OJ .
Are you saying what I think you 're saying ?
♪ ♪
I 'm telling you , man , we don 't need a lot .
We just need enough to make our shit
look different from what 's out there .
You get what I 'm saying ? Like ...
You know I ain 't trying to run it up .
I just was looking online , and I seen a lot of shit .
OJ : You know I 'm broke , right ?
- EMERALD : We 'll use my money . - ( LAUGHS )
Okay , shut up . Look .
All right .
There it is . Five to a hundred K.
- Well , read it . - You read it , dyslexic ass .
The point is a website like Cyber Dominion
will pay five to a hundred K
for photographic evidence of UFOs and shit .
A hundred K ?
And that 's just what I saw on the first go .
Now that I 'm thinking about it , fuck Cyber Dominion .
This shit right here is a moment .. Our moment .
We set it up , release it the right way ,
man , I 'm talking rich and famous for life .
How you doing ? You look pretty .
She look like she got a big house .
- How ? - How what ? How we put it out ?
- Mm . - Well , that 's what I 'm saying .
We don 't just go for the quick cash-in , okay ?
We-we go to the most credible platform to do the story .
- What 's that ? Like Oprah ? - Yeah .
Like Oprah , for example . After that , everybody want in .
Well , I 'm saying there 's plenty
of videos of flying shit online .
I saw one the other day . That wasn 't on Oprah .
Nigga , I didn 't say Oprah . You said Oprah .
You love Oprah .
Look , all I 'm saying is all that shit online is fake .
Low quality . Ain 't nobody gonna get what we gonna get .
What we gonna get ?
- The shot . - What shot ?
The shot . The money shot .
Undeniable , singular , the ...
- the Oprah shot . - The Oprah shot ?
MAN : Excuse me .
Hi . I can help you over here .
Hi .
- Thank you for shopping at Fry 's . - ( SCANNER BEEPING )
Did you guys find everything you 're looking for today ?
Yes ... Angel .
Oh . Great .
Um , actually , do you have a card with us ?
EMERALD : No , thank you .
Uh , would you like one ?
- Because it ... - No , thank you .
Would you like one of our tech support personnel
to help you with the installation ?
No , no , no , no , no , thank you .
Appreciate you .
All right , uh , no help with the install .
Suit yourself . ( CHUCKLES )
Is it a hard install ?
Well , for me , no .
You 're not gonna be able to do it .
What happened ? Did you guys get robbed ?
- OJ : Mm-hmm . - Yeah , you know .
A lot of blackouts .
Take the camera out from time to time .
All these new cameras , they have backup battery power ,
so you should be fine .
But the outages affect the power in the battery shit , too ,
like cell phones .
( CHUCKLING ) : Okay . All right .
Cell phones , they don 't just drop in power . Right ?
I mean , maybe your Wi-Fi drops out
whenever your system dips .
So , that 's technology .
Okay , or maybe you 're in a UFO hot spot . ( CHUCKLES )
( CHUCKLES ) No one believes in that .
( YAWNS )
What 's up ?
Damn . Did not realize you guys were this far out .
OJ : Mm-hmm .
I don 't mind , though .
Smell of horse shit and fresh air .
Right ?
( SIGHS )
- ( YELLS ) - Whoa , whoa , whoa ,
- whoa , whoa , whoa . - ( YELL ECHOES )
Whoa . Look at me , man .
- Fuck . - Don 't do that . Don 't yell .
Sorry , man .
Sorry if I was , like , a little shut down this morning .
Just got out of a four-year relationship .
You were fine .
I know it 's gonna sound fucking cliché , all right ,
but I thought that she was the one , you know ?
Is this gonna take longer than an hour ?
This ? Oh , shit , yeah .
- I 'm-a go ahead and pop out . - Where you going ?
I got to go to the store and get something .
Don 't worry about it . You need anything ?
Yo .
Her name was , uh , Rebecca Diaz .
Yep , keep an eye out for her .
She 's an actress , model , you know ?
She booked a pilot on The CW , so ...
Yeah , fucking left me .
( CHUCKLES , SNIFFS )
Yeah , fucking CW .
- So , thing about this camera ... - Actually , can it swivel up ?
- Uh , yeah . - ( WHIRRING )
- Boom . - Little more ?
- More . Okay . - ( WHIRRING )
- ( CHUCKLES ) Yeah . - ( OJ CLICKING TONGUE )
OJ : Mm .
Uh , yeah .
( CAMERA WHIRRING )
OJ : Mm-hmm .
Do you know they don 't call ' em UFOs anymore ?
It 's fucking UAPs now .
Why they got to change the name ?
( CHUCKLES ) : Yeah .
Exactly .
No , fuck it . I-I 'll tell you why
they changed the name , all right ?
It-it 's ' cause they want to keep us in the dark .
Remember when they declassified
all that UFO footage a couple years ago ?
Yeah . Well , people started paying attention .
So they changed the name to UAPs .
And no one knows what the fuck a UAP is ,
so everyone lost interest .
I saw that .. That Navy clip .
Couldn 't really see ' em , though .
Could 've been better .
It 's shitty footage of exact proof
that there 's an alien civilization
out there in the universe .
So , who 's that ?
Come on , man . The little guys with the big eyes .
- Mm . - Yeah .
There 's lots of theories .
Either they 're intergalactic travelers looking for peace
or futuristic humans coming back in time
to stop us from destroying the planet ,
or they 're fucking world killers .
Planetary destroyers .
And that means that they 've been fucking watching us
and studying us , waiting for the perfect time to beam us up
and shove metal probes up our fucking asses .
Cool .
An-Anyway , Ancient Aliens , History Channel .
- Watch that shit . - EMERALD ( IN DISTANCE ) : Hey !
Hey !
Come on ! Help a nigga out !
Hey .
Know where I could find me a couple of big , strong fellas ?
You good ?
I 'm good .
- What ? - What 's that ?
Oh , this ?
You know , just , uh , training horses we ordered
that I picked up .
- Where 'd you get it from ? - Don 't worry about it .
Now , come on , help me out .
Got you .
Okay , so ... so what is that ?
- Is it like bait ? - I told you .
It is a decoy for horse training .
ANGEL : Okay .
Shit . Shit .
- See ? - OJ .
We good . I mean , he don 't know shit .
Oh , no . You guys are doing something shady .
( HORN HONKS )
JUPE : Hey there !
Hey !
You can stay right there , though !
Sure !
What 's up ?
EMERALD : We 're setting up a decoy !
For horse training !
Oh , good !
You know , we got some of those !
( METAL CREAKING )
Where 'd you get ...
Where 'd you get yours ? !
Yeah ... I 'm not really sure !
My wife would know !
- Okay ! Thanks for stopping by ! - Why the ... Shh .
You don 't live here .
Sorry . Trying to help .
JUPE : Sure thing !
Hey . I wanted to invite you to our ...
new family live show !
Friday ! At 5 : 00 p.m. !
Okay !
Thumbs u ... thumbs up .
Should I do it ?
Yeah , do it .
Thumbs up !
ANGEL : And so , the router 's in the shed .
I set it up so if the power goes down on camera A ,
camera B 's pointed at the sky to catch
whatever might have taken it out .
And , uh , vice versa , so ...
Thank you .
I mean , you 're really not gonna tell me
what the fuck is going on ?
( OJ CHUCKLES )
- You 'll know soon enough . - ANGEL ( CHUCKLING ) : Oh .
Cool , cryptic .
( QUIETLY ) : Fucking dicks .
I can monitor the feeds remotely myself , if you want .
Free of charge .
- Hell no . - No .
( QUIETLY ) : Wham , bam , thank you , ma 'am .
- ( ANGEL SIGHS ) - ( VAN DOOR OPENS )
One more thing .
You 'll be getting a call from my supervisor
asking how my service was .
Five stars , Angel . Five stars .
Thank you .
( ENGINE STARTS )
( VAN DEPARTING )
- ( SIGHS ) So , what now ? - I don 't know .
- What you want to do ? - I 'm .. Whatever you want to do .
Well , I got some work I got to do .
- I 'm gonna go out ... - ( CHUCKLES )
That 's a good one .
( INSECTS TRILLING )
( METALLIC CREAKING )
♪ Fisherman , row ♪
♪ Keep on rowing your boat ♪
♪ Brother man , brother man , yeah , row ... ♪
OPRAH ( ON TV ) : I 'm talking today to women who say
they have been abducted by aliens from another planet .
WOMAN ( ON TV ) : May I briefly say , I don 't know for a fact
that they 're from another planet .
OPRAH : Well , you know you weren 't
- in Kansas anymore , Toto . - ( LAUGHTER ON TV )
WOMAN : And I wasn 't wearing red shoes
- that I could click together , either . - Yeah , yeah .
♪ Living in a bamboo hut ♪
♪ In a little old seaport town ♪
( HORSE SHRIEKING IN DISTANCE )
♪ Three kids on the floor ... ♪
- ( MACHINERY WHIRRING ) - ( SPRINKLERS SPRAYING )
( HORSE HUFFS )
( SNIFFS )
( HORSE NEIGHS )
- ( MACHINERY POWERS DOWN ) - ( SPRINKLERS STOP )
( SIGHS )
- ( MACHINERY POWERS UP ) - ( SPRINKLERS SPRAYING )
( HOLLOW , METALLIC THUMPING )
( HORSE WHINNIES )
( CHITTERING )
( RHYTHMIC SQUEAKING )
♪ ♪
( HORSE GRUNTS )
( RHYTHMIC SQUEAKING CONTINUES )
( CELL PHONE BUTTONS BEEPING )
( CHITTERING )
( RHYTHMIC SQUEAKING )
( CHITTERING AND SQUEAKING CONTINUES )
Nope . Mm-mm . Nope , I 'm out .
I 'm going . Fuck this shit .
( PANTING )
Okay . Okay .
( CHITTERING AND SQUEAKING STOP )
( HORSE WHINNIES )
( CHITTERING )
( LOUD , RHYTHMIC SQUEAKING )
( GRUNTS )
Ow .
( PANTING )
( LAUGHS )
- BOY : Oh , shit ! - BOY 2 : Fuck off .
( THROUGH VOICE SCRAMBLER ) : Give us back our property .
- Don 't mess with Jupiter 's Claim ! - Come on .
( BOYS LAUGHING , HOWLING )
- ( CELL PHONE BEEPS ) - ( FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING )
EMERALD : What happened ?
The Park kids .
Jupe 's sons .
And they let Clover out , man .
What ? They trying to prank Haywood ?
- It 's on ! - Hey . You stole their horse .
Oh .
Yeah .
( KEYS JINGLING )
( DOOR CLOSES )
♪ ♪
- Hey . - Shit .
Oh .
What 's up , Nessie ?
Not much . Just stocking shit .
You know , pretty much regular .
♪ ♪
( WIND WHISTLING SOFTLY )
( WHISTLES )
( HORSE NEIGHING IN DISTANCE )
( SIGHS )
Oh , shit !
( CHUCKLING )
( CONTINUES CHUCKLING )
I need to take my ass to bed .
- ( CONTINUES CHUCKLING ) - ( CELL PHONE VIBRATING )
- Who this ? - Yo , it 's Angel from Fry 's .
Just calling to tell you that there is a bug on camera A.
I know . Wait , I thought I told you not to watch our shit .
Yeah , I know , I know .
Camera B is down .
What ?
Like Ancient-fucking-Aliens down .
( CLICKS TONGUE )
- ( HORSE NEIGHING ) - ( OJ GRUNTS )
- ( METAL CREAKING ) - ( WIND GUSTING )
( NEIGHING )
( DISTANT RUMBLING )
( BUZZING )
( PANTING )
( HORSE SHRIEKING WILDLY IN DISTANCE )
- Hey ! - ANGEL : Hey . Hi . ( STAMMERS )
Emerald , can you please get the bug off the thing ?
Get the bug off the fucking thing !
( QUIETLY ) : Shit .
( HORSE NEIGHING )
- ( HORSES NEIGHING FRANTICALLY ) - ( THUMPING )
ANGEL : Um , what do you see ?
Do you ... do you see , like , lights or anything ?
Like , a-a fucking saucer ?
It 's in the cloud . It 's in the cloud .
OJ ! It 's in the cloud !
Mm-hmm .
( LOW GROWLING )
( HOWLING ROAR )
Yeah , nah , nah , nah .
Run , OJ ! Run !
- Shit . - ( RUMBLING )
( RUMBLING )
( PANTING )
( WIND WHISTLING SOFTLY )
( RAPID HOOFBEATS )
( NEIGHING )
( GASPING SOFTLY )
Hello ?
NESSIE : What happened to OJ ?
It 's fine .
Come on .
Okay , it 's still on .
The camera , it 's still on .
♪ ♪
Shit , shit , shit , shit , shit .
Okay , you fucking praying mantis .
All right , bitch .
You like Sour Patch Kids ?
Huh ?
( GRUNTING )
♪ ♪
( RUMBLING )
( WIND WHISTLING SOFTLY )
♪ ♪
( HOOFBEATS GALLOPING )
( HORSE NEIGHS )
- ( WILD SHRIEKING ) - ( BOOMING , RUMBLING )
- ( GASPS ) - ( SHRIEKING IN DISTANCE )
( WILD SHRIEKING IN DISTANCE )
( SHRIEKING FADES )
( QUIET , TREMBLING BREATHS )
( BREATH TREMBLING ) : A 'ight , man .
Where your shit ? Let 's go .
Haven 't seen one of those in a minute .
Fucking praying mantis .
That motherfucker better pray I don 't ever see him ,
' cause if I do , I 'm-a eat him .
- Let 's go . - Where ?
Man , I don 't know .
( STAMMERS ) I got me a little situation in At water
texting me back right now .
- It 's not coming again tonight . - I don 't care .
No . No .
No .
Bro , I ain 't never seen no shit like this .
It ain 't worth it .
No , nope . It 's too much .
You should go , then .
I got to get up early anyway .
I got mouths to feed .
( SHUDDERING EXHALE )
Shit .
- Shit , shit , shit ! - ( HORSE NEIGHING FAINTLY )
( HORSES NEIGHING )
You hear that ?
( NEIGHING CONTINUES )
Ghost out there .
Acting all territorial .
OJ : Mm .
I guess some animals ain 't fit to be trained .
( HORSE HUFFS , NEIGHS IN DISTANCE )
( MACHINE WHIRRING )
( PHONE VIBRATING )
- Hello ? - EMERALD : Uh , hi .
Is this , uh , Antlers Holst ?
ANTLERS : Who 's this ?
Hey , yeah . I 'm Emerald Haywood .
Uh , we met a couple days ago at the commercial .
- Oh , yeah , horse girl . Sure . - ( EMERALD CHUCKLES )
I remember you and your brother .
EMERALD : Yeah , horse boy .
He 's here , too .
- The descendants of the jockey . - Yeah .
ANTLERS : Guess I 'm talking to motion picture royalty , then .
How 'd you get the number ?
- I got it from the call sheet . - Ah .
So , we have a project , and , uh ,
you know , what if I told you it was the offer of a lifetime ?
ANTLERS : Yeah , hopefully not my lifetime .
That 's a good one . Um , I 'm-a be real with you .
We don 't have a lot of money to pay you up front ..
You know , not like you 're used to .. But , uh ...
Yeah . I tend to do one for them so I can do one for me ,
so what is it ?
- Reality . - Oh , no . Reality .
Documentary .
- Doc-Documentary . - ANTLERS : Oh , that 's better .
- So , again , what 's it about ? - ( CHUCKLES )
It 's about the shit dreams is made of , baby .
ANTLERS : Listen , horse girl .
- I got a , uh ... - ( MACHINE WHIRRING )
... pretty damn superb lemon tart in the oven
I 'm about to serve to ten of my closest friends , so ...
( WHISPERS ) : Stop .
- Stop , stop , stop . - Oh , hold on one second . What ?
- He 's not here for that . - Look , look , no .
OJ : Don 't be cute . Stick to the plan . Say it !
EMERALD : This is what I do . I don 't go to your job
and knock a horse 's dick out your damn hand .
- Hello ? ( CHUCKLES ) - ANTLERS : Yeah .
EMERALD : Yeah , my bad . We good , man .
Um , according to American Cinema magazine ,
you make the cinematically impossible possible .
Well , we looking for the impossible shot .
- ( BUTTON CLICKS ) - ( MACHINE STOPS )
That 's impossible .
Antlers .
There 's something out here in Agua Dulce ,
and you 're probably the only person in the world
that can get it on film .
Th-That 's it .
Horse girl , this dream you 're chasing ,
the one where you end up at the top of the mountain ,
all eyes on you
it 's the dream you never wake up from .
( TAPS PHONE )
( MACHINE WHIRRING )
( LINE BEEPING )
I don 't like him .
- ( EMERALD SIGHS ) - ( CLICKS TONGUE )
- ( VEHICLE APPROACHING ) - ( ROCK MUSIC PLAYS OVER STEREO )
♪ ♪
( DOOR OPENS , CLOSES )
Holy shit . It 's real .
EMERALD : I don 't know what you 're doing here , but ...
it was illegal for you to ...
spy on us like that .
( SIGHS )
Wait , you ... you don 't know ?
Okay , uh , tell me when you see it .
There .
- Doesn 't move . - ANGEL : Exactly .
EMERALD : Well , look at that .
ANGEL : Yeah . Yeah , yeah , okay .
I went back and scrubbed through the footage ,
and that cloud has been right there
at least since I set the cameras up .
OJ : Yeah , now you mention it ,
I 've probably been looking at the same damn cloud
every day for the last six months .
EMERALD : Shit .
So , I mean , that 's them in there .
And we 've been recording it , so we got it .
Right ?
Yeah .
Why you saying " yeah " like that ?
I mean , we have proof of aliens on video . I ...
Yeah , I wouldn 't call it proof .
Are you serious ?
Look , I 've seen crazy weather phenomenons online before .
- That 's all I 'm saying . - He 's right .
It 's good , but it ain 't it . Ain 't Oprah .
( EMERALD SIGHS )
Ain 't Oprah .
ANGEL : Okay . Are you guys telling me
that there 's an alien spaceship
in that fucking cloud right there ?
OJ : It doesn 't move like a ship .
EMERALD : What you mean , OJ ?
OJ : What if it 's not a ship ?
( QUIET , INDISTINCT CHATTER )
( GORDY HOOTING SOFTLY )
TRAINER : All right , Gordy , we 're almost ready , buddy .
- Here we go , buddy . Come on . - ( CHATTER CONTINUES )
- He 's ready . - DIRECTOR : Set .
Here we go .
And ... action .
And , of course , I set it to Icelandic time
because we share a love of the aurora borealis , Gordy .
And you have no idea how to tell time .
- ( AUDIENCE LAUGHING ) - Great gift , Dad .
Way to think things through .
Somehow , you 'd think that a man who can send
a rocket into space would be able to manage
a halfway decent birthday present .
Nope .
( AUDIENCE LAUGHING )
You know , Gordy , all things considered ,
maybe my gift isn 't so bad after all .
- Aw . - AUDIENCE : Aw .
- Hey , Gordy . - ( PHYLLIS GASPS )
- Surprise ! - PHYLLIS : Wow .
- Now , that is a gift . - ( AUDIENCE LAUGHING )
( GORDY PANTING )
Oh . Sorry . My ...
DIRECTOR : That 's all right . Pick it up from there .
Wait a minute .
What happened to we both failed at finding good presents ?
( AUDIENCE LAUGHING )
Here you go , Gordy . Happy birthday .
- ( GASPS ) Oh , beautiful , Hayley . - ( GORDY PANTING EXCITEDLY )
- ( LAUGHTER ) - ( AUDIENCE APPLAUDING )
( WHOOPING )
- ( BALLOON POPS ) - ( GORDY SCREECHING FRANTICALLY )
- ( OBJECTS CRASHING ) - TOM : Whoa , hey , hey , hey . No .
- No , no ! Down ! Down ! Gordy ! - TRAINER : Down !
- MARY JO : No . Stop ! - TRAINER : Stop that !
- ( PANICKED SHOUTING ) - ( PEOPLE SCREAMING )
( BELL RINGING STEADILY )
( SLOW THUMPING )
( RUSTLING )
( CLACKING , THUMPING )
- ( SOFT THUMPING ) - ( GORDY PANTING )
( GORDY HOOTING QUIETLY )
( SQUISHING )
♪ ♪
- ( BALLOON POPS ) - ( OBJECTS CLATTERING )
( HEAVY THUMPING )
( MARY JO WHIMPERS , GASPS )
- ( SHUDDERING BREATHS ) - ( HEAVY THUMPING )
- ( MARY JO GRUNTING IN PAIN ) - ( BALLOON POPS )
( MARY JO GROANING , PANTING )
( HOOTS QUIETLY )
( SHUDDERING BREATHS )
( MARY JO WHIMPERING )
( MARY JO SCREAMS )
( HEAVY THUMPING , SQUISHING )
( FLESH SQUISHING )
( FOOTSTEPS )
TOM : Oh , no . No , no , no , no .
No , no , no , no , no . No , Gordy , no ! No !
- D-D-Down ! Down ! Down ! - ( GORDY HOOTING FRANTICALLY )
- You sit ! Down . - ( GORDY SCREECHING )
No , no , no .
( TOM WHIMPERING )
- No , no , no ! - ( OBJECTS CRASHING )
- No , Gordy ! - ( GORDY SCREECHING )
Stop ! Ah !
- No ! No ! - ( HEAVY THUMPING )
( GASPING BREATHS )
( HEAVY THUMPING CONTINUES )
( BALLOON POPS )
( FOOTSTEPS )
( PANTING )
( GASPING BREATHS )
( GORDY PANTING )
( HOOTING )
- ( INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER ) - ( GUNSHOT )
( SIRENS WAILING IN DISTANCE )
( URGENT CHATTER )
MAN : Seven just on scene .. Oh , my God .
♪ ♪
( CHATTER AND SIRENS CONTINUE )
( BIRDS CHIRPING )
♪ ♪
( JUPE TAKES DEEP BREATH )
( JUPE SIGHS )
( CHUCKLES )
Feeling good ?
Yeah .
Feeling good .
Good .
( AMBER CLEARS THROAT )
( WHISPERS ) : There we go .
Run it . Run it one more time , babe .
Okay .
( TAKES DEEP BREATH )
What if I told you ...
Yo . It 's , uh ... Storm 's coming .
Just tarping up , just to be safe .
( PAPER RUSTLING )
♪ ♪
Hey , where you going ?
I 'm-a get Lucky .
AMBER : Now , we 're not gonna let
a few clouds kill our fun today , are we , folks ?
So , without further ado ,
welcome to the Jupiter 's Claim Star Lasso Experience !
( AUDIENCE CHEERING )
JUPE : How 's everyone feeling today ?
All right .
It 's quite a doozy today .
Uh , I want to thank you guys for coming out here .
But first , how about another round of applause
for my Amber ?
- ( APPLAUSE ) - I 'll tell you , that woman is
a saint for putting up with all my craziness .
And to the knuckleheads up there .
- The staff . Shout-out . - ( WHOOPING , EXCITED SHOUTING )
All right , all right .
That 's enough . ( CHUCKLES )
I also want to give a special thanks to
an old costar of mine and my first crush ,
Mary Jo Elliott , everyone !
- ( SCATTERED CHEERS ) - Yeah .
All right .
- You ready ? - ( CROWD MURMURING )
Oh , come on . That ain 't nothing .
- Are you ready ? ! - ( FEEDBACK SQUEALS )
( CHEERING , APPLAUSE )
Here we go .
( DRAMATIC WESTERN MUSIC PLAYS )
( EXHALES )
( WHISPERS ) : You 're chosen .
What if I told you ...
that in about an hour ...
you 'll leave here different ?
See , every Friday for the last six months ,
my family and I have bore witness
to an absolute spectacle .
One that you 'll be seeing here today .
So let me take you back to that first night .
( SIGHS )
( KEY CLICKS )
( ROUSING ORCHESTRAL MUSIC PLAYS )
Right here in this exact spot ,
I 'd come over to wrangle a chestnut horse named Trigger .
Now , I could barely see my hand in front of my face
for the fog , but I swear
on my wife and children 's lives
that at 6 : 13 p.m. ,
I see
a flying saucer
descend through the mist .
Old Trigger took off straight into the gulch .
And , well
it 's like he was going home .
( SNAPS FINGERS )
- ( APPLAUSE ) - ( LUCKY HUFFS SOFTLY )
Now , just to be clear , what we saw
was a flying saucer .
No doubt about that .
Slightly flatter in the front ,
with a circular hole in the bottom
about two school bus lengths wide .
Ladies and gentlemen , I kid you not .
We are being surveilled
by an alien species I call " the Viewers . "
And though they have yet to emerge from their ship ,
I believe they trust me .
If they didn 't , I don 't think any of us
would be here right now .
( LAUGHING )
So , as I said , in just under an hour ,
Star Lasso Experience is gonna change you .
( ROUSING ORCHESTRAL MUSIC ENDS )
But first , my boys are gonna come out
and do a little number for us . Would that be all right ?
- AMBER : Hustle . Go , go , go . - ( APPLAUSE ) - ( BOYS HOWLING )
JUPE : All right . My little satellites :
- Colton , Phoenix , Max . - ( UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYS )
Remember those names , folks .
All right , here we go !
( JUPE 'S VOICE ECHOES FAINTLY )
( SOFT RUSTLING )
( LOUD ROARING )
MAN ( IN AUDIENCE ) : What is that ?
Do you guys see that ?
♪ ♪
( DEEP ROARING )
Uh , uh , stay in your seats .
This is new .
- Uh , they 're early . - ( LUCKY WHINNIES SOFTLY )
They 're giving us a real show today .
- JUPE : That they are . - AMBER ( CHUCKLES ) : Yeah .
They 're ready , we 're ready .
ANNOUNCER ( RECORDED ) : Welcome to the Star Lasso Experience ,
- only at Jupiter 's Claim . - ( JUPE CLICKS TONGUE )
- Please remember to avoid ... - Come on .
... using your cell phones or any flash photography ...
- Cell phones off , y 'all . - ... during the event .
( CLICKS TONGUE ) Come on !
AMBER : Bear with us now .
Trained animals can be unpredictable .
( AMBER CHUCKLES )
( ROUSING ORCHESTRAL MUSIC PLAYS )
( BREATHING DEEPLY )
ANNOUNCER : Now sit back , stay in your seats and enjoy
( SLOWING , DISTORTING ) : The Star Lasso Experien ...
( MACHINES POWER DOWN )
( GASPING , MURMURING )
( DEEP ROARING )
( CHITTERING , THUMPING )
- ( LUCKY NEIGHING ) - ( PEOPLE SCREAMING )
( PANICKED SHOUTING )
( PANICKED SCREAMING , FRANTIC CHATTER )
( ROARING GROWS LOUDER )
- ( PEOPLE SCREAMING ) - ( DEEP GROWLING )
- ( SHARP THUD ) - ( SCREAMING STOPS )
( PEOPLE SCREAMING FAINTLY )
( DEEP GROWLING )
- ( PANICKED SCREAMING , SHOUTING ) - ( DEEP SQUELCHING )
( WOMAN WHIMPERING , CRYING )
( DEEP SQUELCHING )
( WOMEN GROANING , RETCHING )
( PEOPLE SCREAMING )
( DEEP SQUELCHING )
( SOBBING )
( PEOPLE SCREAMING )
( PANICKED SCREAMING )
( ORCHESTRAL MUSIC PLAYING QUIETLY )
JUPE ( RECORDED ) : Well , cowboys and cowgirls ,
it 's time to ride off into the sunset .
That 's right . Happy trails .
It 's closing time .
You don 't have to go home , but you can 't stay here .
Come back again .
And until then , we wish you well .
Hasta la vista . Adios .
- ( MUSIC CONTINUES ) - ( PIG SQUEALING NEARBY )
JUPE ( RECORDED ) : Well , cowboys and cowgirls ,
it 's time to ride off into the sunset .
That 's right . Happy trails .
It 's closing time .
You don 't have to go home , but you can 't stay here .
Come back again .
And until then ...
( LUCKY NEIGHING )
( LUCKY HUFFS )
( NEIGHING CONTINUES )
( SMACKING LIPS RAPIDLY )
Lucky .
( WIND WHISTLING SOFTLY )
( SOFT WHISTLING IN DISTANCE )
Lucky .
( SMACKING LIPS RAPIDLY )
( NEIGHING )
Lucky , come on , come on . Come on !
( SOFT WHISTLING CONTINUES IN DISTANCE )
( SOFT POPPING )
( RAPID POPPING )
( PEOPLE SCREAMING IN DISTANCE )
- ( NEIGHING ) - ( SMACKING LIPS RAPIDLY )
( WHISPERING ) : Come on , come on , come on .
Lucky . ( SMACKS LIPS )
( NEIGHS )
( WHOOSHING , FAINT SCREAMING IN DISTANCE )
( LUCKY NEIGHS )
Come on , come on , come on , come on , come on , come on .
- ( LOUD RUMBLING ) - ( LUCKY SHRIEKING WILDLY )
( PEOPLE SCREAMING )
( OJ SCREAMS , GRUNTS )
( ELECTRICITY BUZZING )
♪ ♪
( SOFT WHOOSHING IN DISTANCE )
( HOOVES CLOPPING )
( LUCKY NICKERING )
( DOOR CLOSES )
Yo . ( SIGHS )
It 's done .
All right , I 'll be over in the morning to tear that shit off .
Or you guys can do it yourselves .
- It 's all the same . - No , no .
- I like when you do it . - Of course you do .
All right . See you tomorrow .
- See you . - ( DOOR OPENS , CLOSES )
( GRUNTS )
( PANTING )
- ( LINE RINGING ) - Pick up , pick up , pick up ,
pick up , pick up , pick up , pick up .
Come on , come on . Pick up , pick up , pick up .
( ENGINE STARTS )
( " SUNGLASSES AT NIGHT " BY COREY HART PLAYING )
OTIS SR . ( ON VIDEO ) : Did you know that
the very first assembly of photographs
in sequential order to make a motion picture
was a two-second clip of a Black man on a horse ?
- ( PHONE VIBRATING ) - That man was a Bahamian jockey
known as Alistair E. Haywood ,
and he was my great-great-grandfather .
- Hey . - OJ ( ON PHONE ) : Em .
I was right .
It 's not a ship .
What happened ?
♪ I wear my sunglasses at night ♪
( SLOWING , DISTORTING ) : ♪ So I can , so ... ♪
( ENGINE AND MUSIC STOP )
What the fuck ?
- ( SIGHS ) - ( SOFT WHOOSHING IN DISTANCE )
♪ ♪
Shit .
It ate them , Em .
It ate them all .
It 's alive , Em . It 's an animal .
It 's territorial , and it thinks
( SLOWING , DISTORTING ) : That this is its home .
- Em ! - ( LINE BEEPING )
( YELLS )
Oh , fuck . ( PANTING )
Oh , shit .
Ooh , yes .
Hey , hey . We 're in trouble .
Okay ?
Oh , fuck .
Shit .
- ( PEOPLE SCREAMING IN DISTANCE ) - ( EMERALD SHUDDERING )
What ?
( WHOOSHING )
( SCREAMING CONTINUES )
( RUMBLING )
( WHIMPERS )
( SCREAMING CONTINUES )
What the fuck ?
( SHUDDERING BREATHS )
ANGEL : Who the hell is that ?
Who the hell is that ?
- Em ! Who the hell is that ? - Fuck .
( SCREAMING CONTINUES )
( WHISPERS ) : It 's above us .
- ( LOUD ROARING ) - ( PEOPLE SCREAMING LOUDLY )
Ah , shit !
Shit .
- ( ROARING , SCREAMING CONTINUE ) - Oh , shit ! What the fuck ?
( PANICKED SCREAMING , SHOUTING )
- ( SCREAMING STOPS ) - ( SQUISHING )
( DEEP GRUMBLING )
( OBJECTS CREAKING , CLATTERING )
ANGEL : Oh , God .
S-Something very bad is happening .
( SCREAMS )
Fuck !
( THUNDER CRASHING )
( RUMBLING , SQUISHING )
ANGEL ( WHIMPERING ) : Yeah , we 're fucked .
♪ ♪
( THUNDER CRASHING )
( ENGINE STOPS )
( WATER RUSHING OUTSIDE )
( GASPING BREATHS )
( RUSHING WATER FADES )
( WHIMPERING )
( RUMBLING )
( DEEP GROANING )
( LUCKY NEIGHING )
- ( LUCKY HUFFING ) - ( GROANING FADES )
( PANTS QUIETLY )
( DEEP GROWLING )
( ROARING )
Nope .
( GASPS )
♪ ♪
( METAL CREAKING )
( SOFT POPPING , ECHOING )
( METALLIC CREAKING )
( LOCK CLICKS )
( BIRDS CHIRPING )
- ( ELECTRONICS POWERING UP ) - ( DISTORTED MUSIC PLAYING )
- ( LUCKY NEIGHS ) - ( GASPS )
( METAL CREAKING )
( DISTORTED ) : ♪ I wear my sunglasses at night ♪
♪ So I can ... ♪
( ENGINE STARTS )
( DISTORTED MUSIC CONTINUES )
( NICKERS )
( DISTORTED ) : ♪ It cuts my security ♪
♪ Has she got ♪
♪ Control of me ? ♪
♪ I turn to her and say ... ♪
ANGEL : Em . OJ 's coming .
EMERALD : Let 's go .
( WHISPERING ) : Got to get out this house .
I got to get out this house .
No , st-st-stop . Can 't we just wait , right ?
- You can . - No , I 'm not gonna be here alone .
- I 've got to get out this fucking house ! - No .
We 're alive still because we stayed here .
( DISTORTED MUSIC CONTINUES )
( ENGINE STOPS )
( METAL CREAKING )
( DISTORTED MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING IN VAN )
( EMERALD AND ANGEL ARGUING INDISTINCTLY IN DISTANCE )
( LUCKY NICKERS )
( DISTORTED MUSIC CONTINUES )
( EMERALD AND ANGEL CONTINUE ARGUING )
( DISTORTED MUSIC CONTINUES LOUDLY )
( DISTORTED ) : ♪ I wear my sunglasses ... ♪
( EMERALD SHOUTS )
EMERALD : Go !
- OJ : Come on . Come on . - EMERALD : Go !
Come on , come on , come on , come on .
- Come on , come on . - ( EMERALD WHIMPERING )
( DISTORTED MUSIC SLOWS TO A STOP )
- ( ANGEL SHUSHING ) - ( EMERALD PANTING )
- EMERALD : Go . - ( SOFT POPPING )
( WHOOSHING )
Yeah , she ... she gonna make it .
- BUSTER : OJ . - She gonna make it .
- Oh , hey , horsie . - OJ : Hey , don 't-don 't look him
- in the eyes , please . - FYNN : VFX !
( NEIGHS )
- ( SOFT WHOOSHING ) - ( EMERALD GRUNTING )
( TAPPING LEG )
- ( FRUSTRATED GRUNT ) - ( TAPPING VAN )
( ANGEL SHUSHES )
( WHISPERING ) : Focus here . Focus here .
- ( EMERALD PANTING ) - Come on .
( MUSIC RESUMES CLEARLY )
- ♪ I wear my sunglasses ♪ - EMERALD : Go !
♪ At night ♪
♪ I wear my sunglasses at night ♪
♪ I cry to you , I ... ♪
( SIGHS )
( MEDIEVAL FLUTE MUSIC PLAYING )
MAN ( OVER SPEAKERS ) : Welcome to my tavern .
I don 't know if you 've heard , but a terrible beast is about .
It 's been harassing villagers ,
ruining crops and eating their livestock .
( DRAGON ROARS OVER SPEAKERS )
Many a glory-seeking hunter has attempted to defeat it ,
and just as many have perished .
While you 're here ... While you 're here ...
While you 're here , please look around .
♪ ♪
I 'm here in Agua Dulce , California ,
and the whereabouts of those 40 guests and employees
of a local Western theme park are still unknown .
The sheriff 's office has had its hands full
trying to identify the unaccounted for .
Until they do , only one thing is certain .
There is something strange happening
out here in Agua Dulce .
OFFICER ( ON TV ) : Security cameras were off at the time .
Other than that , we have , uh , no reason to suspect foul play .
We did have a considerable amount
of rain come through here ,
so we don 't want to rule out flash flooding
as possibly having played a part . We 're obviously ...
ANGEL : You never go wrong with a fried fish sandwich .
( ANGEL CHUCKLING )
Tartar got tang . ( CHUCKLES )
Stupid .
" Tartar got tang " ?
ANGEL ( CHUCKLING ) : Right ?
I don 't think it eats you if you don 't look it in the eye .
- MAN : Hey , hey ! - ( INDISTINCT ARGUING )
- RTR , bro . - ( MEN CLAMORING OUTSIDE )
You know ?
Like , read the room . ( CHUCKLES )
Nobody want to talk about that .
- MAN : Let 's go ! - MAN 2 : Okay , okay , okay . Enough .
All right , all right , all right , all right , all right .
- ( CLAMORING CONTINUES ) - MAN 3 : Hey , you lucky !
OJ : Every animal got rules .
All right ? We know what it wants ,
and we know how it comes , so ...
Fuck .
We don 't really know shit . ( CHUCKLES )
OJ , what 's this about , man ?
What 's this about ? You want me to ...
You want me to say , " I 'm sorry " ?
" I was wrong " ? " It 's dumb " ?
It wasn 't dumb .
- Own the moment . - Stop .
- Stop , stop this shit . - It was good . It was good .
But the moment about to pass .
And we don 't own shit .
Okay . Well , I assume y 'all are crashing at mine .
Right , ' cause you can .
' Cause I 'm not going back
to the fucking monster umbrella .
- Got to feed ' em . - ( VAN DOOR CLOSES )
Let Lucky out .
There 's shit to do .
Always .
Always some shit to do .
( PHONE DINGS )
♪ ♪
( LUCKY NICKERING )
( SPUTTERS )
( NEIGHING IN DISTANCE )
( OJ SNIFFS )
ANTLERS : There 's a wheelchair on your roof .
Hi .
ANTLERS : That cloud ain 't moved a goddamn inch .
So you 're not completely full of shit .
Thank you .
Yeah . Thank you .
( CLEARS THROAT ) Th-The concept of extraterrestrial animals
in the sky is not a new thing .
You know , people been trying
to get pictures of these things since , like , the ' 50s .
- You know , it 's an ancient ... - How do we see it ?
- It 's gonna get hungry again . - ( SIGHS )
Ah .
So , you know ...
just ring the dinner bell .
( CHUCKLES SOFTLY )
OJ : Now , we know what it doesn 't like .
That little fake horse and flags messed it up good .
Got stuck in its windpipe or something .
I bet it ain 't gonna fuck with flags like that in a minute .
EMERALD : Yeah .
We pissed him off .
OJ : We 're not the reason it settled down here .
That was Jupe .
He got caught up trying to tame a predator .
You can 't do that .
You got to enter an agreement with one .
ANTLERS : Yeah .
Ask Siegfried and Roy .
Okay .
Um , asking as someone who was in the house
- when the shit went down ... - EMERALD : Mm .
How exactly do you enter an agreement with a fucking ...
a UFO , alien entity or whatever the hell you want to call it ?
Jean Jacket .
Call him Jean Jacket .
ANTLERS : So , how about this ?
How about we send ol ' Jean Jacket
some fresh horses in golden hour
- and see what happens ? - ANGEL : Mm-mm .
Horse people .
Mm , why not just set them free ?
We 're not doing that .
Okay .
Who is gonna go down there
and get the star out of his trailer ?
Me .
I 'll get him out .
Where you want it ?
ANTLERS : You draw him out there .
I 'm here .
On this ridge .
Oh , shit .
ANTLERS : Made her myself .
No electricity .
Didn 't I tell you this motherfucker was gonna
come up here with a non-electrical camera ?
Let 's go , boy !
Yeah !
OJ : I 've been up under it a couple times now .
I get him .
It 's an animal .
You don 't turn your back on a bear .
You don 't wear red around a bull .
It 's like that .
You don 't look at it unless you want its attention .
Good night , Mr. Store man .
Fuck it . I call top hat .
OJ : And we ain 't got a lot of time .
One day . Two days , tops .
- ( SIREN WAILING NEARBY ) - ( GRUNTS )
' Cause the word is getting out , and when it does ...
ANGEL : Sorry , dead people . Park 's closed .
OJ : ... you know people gonna come
and do what they always do :
Try and take it all for themselves .
Fine .
Thimble .
That 's the one I wanted anyway .
OJ : Well , let ' em come .
It ain 't gonna matter .
- ( CLICK ) - ( WHIRRING )
' Cause what we about to do
they can 't erase that .
He 's big , he 's bad ,
and he 's got a lot of spirit .
But anything with a spirit can get broke .
So you break it .
I 'll get the shot .
( CHUCKLING )
( ANTLERS SIPS )
ANGEL : Hey , um ...
What we 're doing 's important .
Right ?
Like , what we document , it 's , uh
it 's gonna do some good , huh ?
I mean , besides the money and fucking fame ,
like , we can save some lives .
Fuck , we-we can even save Earth .
Right ?
( ANTLERS CHUCKLES )
- OJ : Mm . - EMERALD : Yeah .
♪ Well , it came down to Earth ♪
♪ And it hid in a tree ♪
♪ I said , " Mr. Purple People Eater ♪
♪ Don 't eat me " ♪
♪ Well , he looked at me and in a voice so gruff ♪
♪ He said , " I wouldn 't eat you ♪
♪ ' Cause you 're too tough " ♪
( CLICKS TONGUE )
♪ He was a one-eyed , one-horned ♪
♪ Flyin ' purple people eater ♪
♪ One-eyed , one-horned ♪
Sure looks strange to me .
( ANTLERS CHUCKLES SOFTLY )
( CLICKING )
( STATIC CRACKLES )
♪ ♪
OJ : He ain 't gonna fuck with you .
( BIRDS CHIRPING )
( BELL CLANGS )
( PANTING )
( FABRIC RUSTLING SOFTLY IN WIND )
( WIND GUSTING SOFTLY )
( ANGEL CLEARS THROAT )
EMERALD : Time to wake up the family .
( RECORD CRACKLING SOFTLY )
( WOLVES HOWLING OVER SPEAKER )
ANGEL ( SIGHS ) : Here we go .
Come out , come out , wherever you are . ( CHUCKLES )
( " EXUMA , THE OBEAH MAN " BY EXUMA PLAYING )
♪ I came down on a lightning bolt ♪
♪ Nine months in my mama 's belly ♪
♪ When I was born , the midwife screamed and shout ♪
♪ I had fire and brimstone coming out of my mouth ... ♪
- ( CHUCKLES ) - ( MUSIC CONTINUES IN DISTANCE )
How exquisitely stupid is that ?
( CHUCKLING )
♪ Na-na-na , na-na-na ♪
♪ Na-na , na-na-na ♪
♪ Exuma was my name when I lived in the stars ♪
♪ Exuma was a planet that once lit Mars ♪
♪ I got the voices of many in my throat ♪
♪ The teeth of a frog and the tail of a goat ♪
♪ I 'm Exuma ♪
♪ I 'm the obeah man ... ♪
- ( SMACKING LIPS ) - ( NEIGHS )
Hah , hah , hah !
♪ Na-na-na , na-na-na ... ♪
( SONG CONTINUES IN DISTANCE )
We gonna get you today , motherfucker .
- ♪ When I 've got my ♪ - ♪ Obeah ♪
- ♪ Big hat on my head ♪ - ♪ Obeah ♪
- ♪ You know that I ♪ - ♪ Obeah ♪
- ♪ Can raise the dead ♪ - ♪ Obeah ♪
♪ And when I got my stick in my hand ♪
♪ You know that I am ... ♪
Where is the feed for Holst 's camera ?
( OVER RADIO ) : Over .
Couldn 't figure it out . Over .
EMERALD : What you mean , you couldn 't figure it out ?
Over .
ANGEL : Um , Holst is shooting on a film camera ,
and all of our cameras are digital , so it 's a whole thing .
Over .
EMERALD : Basically , you forgot about it . Over .
ANGEL : Yeah , well , I had my hands full
rigging 50 fucking sky dancers to dead people 's car batteries
all connected to one control panel .
So , yeah , fucking over . Sorry .
I 'm scared .
Man down .
Man down ? What ? Where ?
OJ : Last dancer , deep in the gulch .
Stay on it , Em . I 'm staying up .
♪ ♪
Motherfucker .
ANGEL : Oh , wait , wait .
Oh , it 's back up .
Could be a faulty battery .
EMERALD : All right . Shot 's up , then .
( SOFT CHITTERING )
Nah , he 's poking .
( MOTOR WHINING )
Who 's this asshole ?
ANGEL : Man in black on a white motorcycle .
No , no , no , no , no , no . Shit .
Can I help you ?
RIDER : You see that cloud ?
Hey , man , who you with ?
RIDER : Oh , I 'm sorry .
Who are you ?
Nobody .
RIDER : You don 't look like a nobody to me .
Yeah , look , w-we doing a camera test
for a Verizon commercial ,
so now I 'm-a need you to clear the road .
RIDER : This whole valley comes up as blurry
on Google Maps .
You 're really tucked away back here .
Jupiter 's Claim ?
Quicker if you go the other way around .
RIDER : Yeah .
Actually ,
what did happen with Jupe Park and all those people ?
He was basically your neighbor , right ?
So , what , they vanished ?
You don 't believe the flood narrative , do you ?
Fuck , guys .
It 's TMZ .
Oh , fuck me .
Uh , hey , guys . Uh , Jean Jacket is definitely in those clouds ,
and he 's definitely coming this way .
RIDER : What 's the matter ? Don 't you want to be on TV ?
EMERALD : Man , I 'm trying to tell you .
You don 't want to go that way .
RIDER : Fuck it .
Your loss , nobody .
- ( SMACKS LIPS ) - ( LUCKY SPUTTERS )
♪ ♪
EMERALD : We still rolling ? Over .
Goddamn right we are .
( PANTING )
Fellas , here it comes . Over .
ANGEL : Pop quiz , guys .
What happens when an electric bike
going 60 miles per hour hits an anti-electric field
going in the opposite direction ?
( MOTOR POWERING DOWN )
( RIDER SCREAMS )
Shit .
Fuck .
ANGEL : Shit . We 're all gonna go to jail .
( ELECTRIC MOTOR WINDING DOWN )
Oh , fuck . There 's no way that that guy 's alive .
( RIDER SCREAMING )
ANTLERS : Ah , shit .
EMERALD : Goddamn .
I told his ass not to go .
- I told him not to go . - ( SMACKING LIPS )
ANGEL : Uh , hey , OJ , what 's ...
Wh-Where the fuck are you going ? ( CHUCKLES )
The fuck is he doing ?
I 'm going dark . Over .
EMERALD : Okay . No , OJ , no . No !
( SLOWING , DISTORTING ) : No self-respecting ...
♪ ♪
( SIGHING )
Whoa , whoa , whoa , whoa , whoa , whoa .
- Hey , hey , hey , hey , hey , hey . Easy , easy , easy . - ( NEIGHS )
RIDER : ( GROANS ) Did you get that on camera ?
- OJ : Look at me . Look at me . Look at me . - What happened ?
OJ : Listen , listen , we-we got to get you out of here .
- Eyes on me . - Where 's my camera ?
- OJ : Hey ! Hey ! - I need my camera .
Do you see it ?
Okay . Angel ?
- What ? - Angel , come on .
We got to reload .
Shit .
( ANTLERS COUGHING )
( RIDER PANTING )
RIDER : Wait .
( MOTORS POWERING UP )
Uh , where 's your phone ?
- ( ELECTRONICS POWERING UP ) - Why aren 't you filming this ?
ANGEL : What ?
ANTLERS : Angel , what 's happening ?
( SIGHS )
Okay , OJ , if you die trying to save that guy ,
I 'll kill you .
RIDER : No . No , no , please .
- Please , no . No . - We 're gonna get you out . Shut your eye .
- Shut your eye . - Not before you take a picture .
( SCREAMS ) T-Take a picture first !
Uh , camera reloads .
( ANTLERS GRUNTS )
RIDER : You can use my camera .
OJ : No , no . There 's not enough time .
( MOTORS POWERING DOWN )
ANGEL ( SINGSONGY ) : It 's here .
( SHUDDERING BREATHS )
RIDER : Be Scorpion King .
Make a name for yourself .
( BOOMING , RUMBLING )
What is that ?
- OJ : My bad , man . - ( GRUNTS ) Hey .
- Oh , my God . - ( GROWLING , CLICKING )
My camera ! I need my camera !
- Oh , my God ! Fuck ! - ( OJ CLICKS TONGUE )
( WHOOSHING )
( RIDER SCREAMING )
ANTLERS : Give me the lid . Give me the lid .
- Come on . All right . - ( RIDER SCREAMING )
RIDER : Oh , God !
ANGEL : Oh , fuck !
Shit ! Fuck !
Hey , hey ! Is everybody okay ?
For the love of fuck , talk to me , please !
EMERALD : OJ .
♪ ♪
OJ . OJ !
You stupid-ass motherfucker , you better answer me .
- ( RIDER SCREAMING ) - OJ : Whoa , whoa , whoa , whoa ,
whoa , whoa , whoa .
EMERALD : Are you okay ? !
( SLOWING , DISTORTING ) : Are you good ? Over .
( RIDER SCREAMING )
- ( GRUFF GRUNTING ) - ( LUCKY NEIGHS )
RIDER : Oh , God ! Oh , God !
Oh , God !
( WHIMPERING ) : Oh , God .
- ( SQUELCHING ) - ( SCREAMING STOPS )
( CLICKING , WHOOSHING )
( GROWLING )
- ( LUCKY NEIGHS ) - ( ROARING )
ANGEL : Holy shit , I-I think it 's taking the dancers .
Are you getting this ?
( OJ CLICKS TONGUE , SMACKS LIPS )
♪ ♪
EMERALD : Guys , OJ 's hooded up .
He 's doing the run . OJ 's doing the run !
ANGEL : Oh , God .
Hey , it 's gone .
I can 't see it anymore , guys .
♪ ♪
- ( GRUNTING ) - ( LUCKY NEIGHING )
( WHOOSHING )
Get it . Get it !
( RUMBLING )
No .
Fuck .
( ROARING )
Go ! Go !
- Lucky , go . Go , go , go , go , go ! - ( LUCKY NEIGHING )
( PANTING )
( BOOMING )
( ANGEL WHOOPS )
Holy shit !
( LAUGHS ) : Yeah !
Let 's go !
Yeah , he didn 't like that , did he ?
ANGEL : OJ , you 're a motherfucking genius .
( PANTING ) : We got it . We got it .
It 's over .
It 's over . We got it , y 'all !
The feed started going in and out when ...
when that guy got got .
But we should be covered with the film camera .
Right , Holst ?
( SIGHS , GRUNTS )
The light .
The light , it 's
gonna be magic soon .
( SCOFFS QUIETLY )
What you mean , Ant ?
Whoa , no , no . Wh-Where you going ?
It 's gonna be all right , Angel .
We don 't deserve the impossible .
( SIGHS )
ANGEL : Uh , hey , guys .
Holst just said some creepy , cryptic shit .
Took his camera . He 's heading up the mountain .
Over .
Hey , Holst .
EMERALD : Holst . Wait . Hold on , man .
Talk to me . What happened ?
Did you get the shot or didn 't you ? Over .
This nigga .
Fuck . ( EXHALES )
This is crazy , right ?
♪ ♪
( SIGHS ) Come on , come on , come on .
Fuck .
- ( BREATHING HEAVILY ) - ( CAMERA RATTLING )
( GASPS )
( STRAINED YELLING )
- ( SCREAMING ) - ( CAMERA CONTINUES RATTLING )
( STRAINED GROANING )
( GRUNTS )
OJ : No , man .
( ROARING )
The fuck ?
( SOFT POPPING )
ANGEL : Holst .
( GROWLING )
( ROARING )
( WHIMPERS , GRUNTS )
( GASPING , GRUNTING )
( COUGHING )
♪ ♪
( SOFT POPPING )
Oh , shit .
( WHIMPERS , SHUDDERS )
( YELLS )
( ROARING )
( SCREAMS )
( SHUDDERS ) Fuck !
( WIND WHISTLING )
( SHUDDERING BREATHS )
ANGEL : Oh .
Oh , God .
No .
Oh , shit .
Fuck .
( GASPS )
What ? ( GRUNTS )
( GROANS )
( GRUNTING , PANTING )
Ow !
( PANTING )
Fuck .
( PAINED GRUNTING )
Okay .
( GASPS ) Fuck !
( YELLS )
( GASPING )
( YELLS ) Oh , shit !
( SCREAMS , WHIMPERS )
- Oh , no ! - ( MELODIC POPPING )
( SCREAMING )
( BOOMING , ROARING )
( GRUNTING )
Don 't look . Don 't look .
Don 't look . Don 't look . Don 't look .
- ( GROANS ) - ( WIND HOWLING )
( GRUNTING )
- ( GROWLING ) - ( PANTING )
OJ : Get the bike !
Get out of here !
( PANTING )
Oh , my God .
You 're dead ! Dead !
Shit , shit , shit , shit . Look down .
( PANTING )
( DEEP GROANING )
( GRUNTS )
( STRAINING )
OJ : Hey .
Whoa . Whoa , whoa , whoa , whoa .
( NEIGHS )
( GRUNTS )
Come on .
( MOTORS POWERING DOWN )
No .
( OJ WHISTLES IN DISTANCE )
♪ ♪
( GROWLING )
( CLICKS TONGUE )
( PANTING )
Oh , fuck . Fuck . Fuck .
♪ ♪
( LUCKY NEIGHING )
EMERALD : No !
( PANTING )
Just leave , OJ .
Forget it ! Come on !
Come on !
( WIND GUSTING )
♪ ♪
( RUMBLING )
( LUCKY SHRIEKS )
( MOTORS POWERING UP )
( LUCKY SHRIEKING IN DISTANCE )
Come on !
( SOFT POPPING )
( GROWLING )
- ( ELECTRICAL WHIRRING ) - ( GRUNTING )
♪ ♪
( GRUNTS )
( SOFT POPPING , CLATTERING IN DISTANCE )
( WOOD CRACKLING )
( GRUNTING )
( YELLS , GRUNTS )
( PANTING )
( WHISPERS ) : It 's gonna fuck you up .
It 's gonna fuck you up .
♪ ♪
( GRUNTING , PANTING )
( GROWLING IN DISTANCE )
( GRUNTING )
( CAMERA CLICKS )
Come on .
Come on , come on ! ( GRUNTS )
♪ ♪
What the ...
( CHITTERING )
( EMERALD GRUNTING , PANTING )
( CAMERA CLICKS )
( PANTING ) : Come on . Come on !
I 'm gonna get you , you motherfucker .
( PANTING )
♪ ♪
- ( GRUNTS ) - ( CAMERA CLICKS )
I 'm-a take you to Oprah . I 'm-a take you to Oprah .
Let 's go to Oprah .
( PANTING )
( WHOOSHING )
♪ ♪
( GRUNTING )
( DEEP GROANING )
- ( YELLS ) - ( CAMERA CLICKS )
( GRUNTS )
( PANTING )
( DEEP SQUELCHING )
( SHARP POP ECHOES )
Yes !
Nobody fucks with Haywood , bitch !
Nobody !
You hear me ? !
( PAINED GRUNTING )
JUPE ( RECORDED , POWERING UP ) : Cowboys and cowgirls ,
it 's time to ride off into the sunset .
- That 's right . Happy trails . - ( GROANING )
It 's closing time .
You don 't have to go home , but you can 't stay here .
Come back again .
Until then , we wish you well .
MAN : Okay , let 's get in there and set up .
- Hasta la vista . Adios . - ( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
MAN : Yeah , get a shot of her . Zoom in .
( CHATTER CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY )
( VEHICLE DOORS CLOSING )
♪ ♪
( CHATTER CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY )
MAN : We 're ready .
MAN 2 : We 're set up , ready to go .
( CHATTER CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY )
MAN : Folks , this is Wally Pachenko
- reporting live from Agua Dulce . - ( PAINED GRUNTING )
Just outside of Jupiter 's Claim ,
where just seconds ago
an inexplicable occurrence , uh , just in the distance ...
You can probably hear th-the shock in my voice .
There are still some fragments , uh , floating in the air
where some-some unidentified object
just drifted off into space and exploded .
Uh , you can see some fragments still falling from the sky .
( VOICE FADING ) : Uh , we will have some amazing ...
( SHUDDERING BREATHS )
♪ ♪
( BREATHING DEEPLY )
( MUSIC ENDS )